PHAN THỊ HÀ

■ 0389676849 | ■ phanthiha0125@gmail.com | 4 25 1st, 2002

R&D Intern



Objective_

In the next 5 years, strive to become an expert in the field of food product research and development. Learn, research further on knowledge related to food product research and development, sensory evaluation. Study sciences for food safety management certification. Enhance and hone soft skills through the work environment.

Education

Hanoi University of Science and Technology - School of Chemistry and Life Sciences

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

4th-year Student - Food Technology Engineering

8/2020 - 7/2024 (Expected)

CPA: 2.93/4.00

Experiences_

Center for Training and Development in Food Technology

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

4/2022 - Current

- Quantifying and establishing processes, formulas for developing new products.
- Improving product quality, innovating packaging, etc.
- Marketing communication of products.

Laboratory of Department of Quality Management

Ha Noi, Viet Nam
4/2022 - Current

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

On the state of sections and the state of th

- Organizing sensory projects for various products (beer, tea, milk, etc.).
- Reporting on sensory seminars.Establishing a Time Intensity sensory panel.

Nutricare Nutrition Joint Stock Company

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

R&D Intern

Intern in the Laboratory

12/2023 - 3/2024

- The establishment of sensory council.
- Researching and exploring the aromatic ingredients within the product.
- · Organizing sensory evaluation sessions.

Heineken Vietnam Brewery Limited Company

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

9/2023 - 12/2023

- Examining several physical properties in beer.
- · Sensory support.
- · Research on PowerApps and Power BI.

Projects_____

The Pepper Sensory Council

Ha Noi, Viet Nam

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

2022 - Current

Planning the selection of the panel, screening the panel, developing a list of sensory descriptors, training on the rating scale. Conducting surveys using forms and utilizing Excel and R for data processing.

Traceability of Pepper Origin

Ha Noi, Viet Nam **2022 - Current**

Vinh Linh Cooperative

This project is implemented in BK Tracking website:

- 1. The establishment of sensory council.
- 2. Researching and exploring the aromatic ingredients within the product.
- 3. Organizing sensory evaluation sessions.

Skills.

Programming R

Office Information MS Word, MS Excel, MS Powerpoint

English B1-VSTEP